Previously on Zombieland Saga Revenge, we were set to open for Iron Frill,
but while we focused on making a big impact,
Shiori, the leader of Iron Frill, threw us all for a loop by trying to recruit Ai to join her group!
No way, sister! Ai is staying with us, and that's all there is to it!
We totally nailed our performance, and then Shiori had the nerve to declare us rivals on live TV!
If that's how she wants to play it, then we're game for revenge!
Let's go, go, go!
Hello! Good morning, everyone!
Uh, and a good morning to you, Lily!
I'm happy to see all your smiling faces!
Although, one of you looks a little bit on the frowny side today!
Me? This is just the way my face was...
Speak up, Kotaro! And remember to enunciate!
Enunciate? What is her deal?
Yeah, what's up, Lily?
Here's the sitch. I want to shine bright! Time for me to step up my game!
We're already hosting a radio show, the Saga Arena concert was a hit,
and Iron Frill declared us to be their rivals!
You've all been working hard to take revenge, which is awesome!
But I want to show up those girls, too!
I thought if I did something extra amazing to showcase my magicalness,
it would take Franjushu to the next level!
For a tiny little thing, you've got plenty of moxie.
So that's it. I've noticed that Lily has had something pressing on her mind lately.
She's been plotting.
You've got my full support!
Do you have something fun planned?
You know it! Check this out!
For the first time ever, Franjushu is gonna move away from the local Saga TV spotlight
onto a national television network program!
Wait! National TV?!
Yeah! This is what I'm talking about!
I'll be entering as a contestant on Japan's Got Performance!
It's a freestyle-type audition show where anything goes!
First competitors from all over the country compete in the regional preliminaries!
If you win there, then you get to enter the national finals held in Tokyo!
Franjushu will finally have a chance to make our big national debut on television!
Yay!
Lily is an expert when it comes to this sort of stuff.
Yeah! You're gonna win that thing for sure!
I'm crazy stoked!
So when does the show start filming?
It's starting right now!
Yay!